Hey, you! Turn around!
Yeah, you with a flat top! Huh? Yeah, you!
You threw this trash, right?
Then, it's a 500 Singapore
dollar fine! No way! 500?
The law here prohibits littering and
fines all violators for doing so,
and that means you!
500 Singapore dollars is...
I think that's gotta be about 40,000
yen. Trash? Are you clear? on that, punk!
Trash?
What are you talking about, sir?
All I see on the ground
here is my own luggage.
So, you've got me a little confused now.
Would you be so kind as to tell me what
trash you're referring to, officer?
If you're wrong, then I'm
obeying the law, right?
So where is it?
You mean that bag is your luggage?
Yeah, you got it.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
Well, I've got to get going, then.
What's up with this kid?
She's still following
us like a lost puppy.
Hey, you.
Weren't you going to see
your father once we got here?
Why don't you stop tagging along and go?
You're here now, so move on.
I'm meeting up with him in five days.
I can go wherever the hell I want.
I'm not taking orders from you jerks.
She mustn't.
She'll be in danger if she stays with us.
Well, maybe she lacks the
cash for a place to stay.
Then that's it.
We'll have to get her a
hotel room for a few nights.
Hey, Polnareff.
Get her to come with us and
try not to bruise her ego.
You got it.
Hey, you're stinking poor, aren't?
you.
Consider this your lucky day, freeloader.
What?
Oh, for God's sake.
Well, let's go
chicken. Okay.
I'm terribly sorry, sir, but we tend
to be full at this time of year.
We no longer have any
large suites available.
May I suggest our double rooms?
I guess we're
Stuck.
Now, for the rooms, uh, Avdol and I
will share a room with each other.
It'd make sense for Jotaro and I to
share a room, since we're both students.
Does that help, Joseph?
Then the last room goes
to Polnareff, and... Huh?
That's just gross!
Like I'd room with that guy! You brat!
Well, she may be a child, but let's
give the young lady her own room.
Excuse me, we'll take four rooms, please.
Yes, of course.
Fine, I can relax more
in my own room anyway.
I'm gonna sleep like a baby tonight.
Let's go!
We've been through all kinds of hell
ever since the day we left Hong Kong.
We should hurry up and take a shower
in a place where it's actually safe.
See ya.
Damn it, I should have guessed.
Couldn't you guys at least give us a
chance to rest, persistent bastards?
Come out!
Climb HIKARI YAKU SADAME
UCHI Cameo NOAH
ONLAND ONLAND
ONLAND ONLAND ONLAND ONLAND
BREAK YOU DOWN KOMBUSH
KOMBUSH Take it now,
I'll be strong to die and die! No!
That's some insanely intense
bloodlust you've got there.
Do me a favor and tell me who you are.
My name's Polnareff, so you'll
know who sent you to hell.
Well, if you insist, my
name is Soul Sacrifice.
And since you're probably wondering,
my stand is the card of the devil.
It represents insanity of the cursed and a
precipitous and malevolent fall into ruin.
But tell me, how did you know
I was hiding inside the fridge?
So you really are that stupid?
You took everything out of the fridge
and didn't bother putting any of it away,
you dumbass!
Die, Polnareff!
Ebony Devil!
Silver Chariot!
Wow, you're really pathetic, aren't you?
That ape on the boat was a far more
terrifying stand user than you.
You realize that you're
worse at this than a monkey?
Now look what you've done, Polnareff.
Damn, how dare you do this to me!
It hurts!
It really, really hurts!
What the hell is with this guy?
Pain!
Curse you!
How dare you!
How dare you do that to me!
Now I can hold one hell
of a grudge against you!
Such torture, such agony must be avenged!
And you're the pathetic one, Polnareff!
I let you find me and
attack me on purpose!
You're dead man now!
He disappeared!
He's gone.
What the hell is going on?
Wait, what?
This is unreal.
When did he cut me?
But I don't think I felt an attack.
No, I'm sure of it.
I didn't feel it.
Mr.
Joestar,
A stand user was here ready to ambush me.
Wait, is that you, Avdol? Anyway, listen.
I couldn't figure him out.
I couldn't tell if he was weak or strong.
He's really creepy.
And he got away.
Dammit, what the hell?
You'd better watch out.
Somehow he was able to cut my leg.
The devil card?
That's soul sacrifice.
Holnorath, are you absolutely
positive that's what he said?
Yeah.
I'm racking my brain.
I just don't see how it's possible.
I know for a fact that I
caught a glimpse of his stand.
The thing is, I don't remember anything
being near me, but my leg's been gouged.
But anyway, I should be
there in five minutes.
You're in room 1212, aren't you?
On the 12th floor?
Contact Kakyoin and Jotaro 2, will you?
Later.
Front desk. Hello there.
Is this room service?
I hurt my leg a bit.
Could you send up some medicine
and bandages as soon as possible?
This is Polnareff, room 912.
Certainly.
We'll bring it up immediately, sir.
Ah, this is the last thing I need.
No matter how you cut it, dirty underwear
makes for a really shitty band-aid.
Damn this hotel.
Avdol, I was wondering, do you know
about this guy who attacked Polnareff?
Yes, he is sole sacrifice.
According to rumors, he's a Native
American shaman who is also an assassin.
But he's an utterly terrifying stand user.
Mafias, militaries, politicians,
lowlifes the world over hire him.
I've seen him before, and he
looks as fierce as his reputation.
His body is covered in scars.
Scars he receives by cunningly
provoking his enemy to attack.
That's how he gets the upper hand.
He uses the so-called power of
vengeance to fully control his stand.
That's why, to ordinary people, it
appears that a curse killed the victims.
So Polnareff must have fallen
for soul sacrifice's trick.
I'm afraid that's what it looks like.
What kind of stand is it?
Nobody knows for certain.
Because those who've seen it are dead, we
have to decide how we're handling this.
Right now, it's too dangerous
for Polnareff to be alone.
Or any of us.
He could try to kill us one by one.
I mean, it's something
he might be able to do.
We need to figure out a strategy.
He'll be here in five minutes.
Let's all meet up in this room.
You got it.
We'll see you in room 1212 soon, old man.
What was that all about, Jojo? Let's go.
Apparently, we're in danger.
What?
Now that's odd.
I can't find my room key.
I could have sworn I
put it down right here.
Am I going crazy?
Damn it. Where is it?
Now how the hell am I
going to get back in here?
Could I tell the front
desk and ask for a new one?
There's probably a fine
for that. There it is.
It must have fallen during
all the commotion earlier.
Why did it have to go all
the way to the middle?
What the?
Hey!
What the hell, shampoo?
Damn it, this is killing my eyes!
Who's there?
Crap, this isn't good.
I'm a sitting duck under here.
Mr.
Polnareff, the front desk sent me up here.
I brought you a first aid kit.
Get away!
You'll get yourself killed!
Sir, what's happened here?
Get out of here!
I told you, you'll get yourself killed!
How dare you!
Polnareff!
How dare you stab one of my eyes out
when I hadn't even touched you once!
Wait, he's a doll?
What kind of stand is that?
Silver Chillion!
You're stupid as you look don't you
get it your stand can't fight where you
can't see as long as you're tied up
underneath the bed you can't hurt me?
Oh, Jojo!
Did you need something?
So you are here. Listen up.
Don't leave this room for a while.
I'll come for you again later.
Keep your door locked, okay?
And don't open it for any strangers.
Oh, okay.
Damn it!
How heavy is this bed anyway?
It's gonna be at least 120 kilograms.
There's no way I can push it off of me.
I've got to use Silver Chariot's
sword to cut these cords
You little bastard as soon as
I stop attacking this happens?
You better believe I'm gonna keep blindly
stabbing every centimeter of this room!
Ah!
Looks like the big scary
knight can't even pin
the tail on the donkey
when he's blindfolded.
Talk about dense.
You're mine now.
Bastards!
I've just about had it
with you, you little runt!
Huh?
It's just you two guys?
Why isn't the girl with you?
Wow.
We went to her room and
made sure she was okay.
We decided against it because
she would be vulnerable.
The risk of her falling under attack while
with us is far too great. Good point.
So we're just waiting
for Polnareff to arrive.
But man, he's so late.
It's already been way over five minutes.
Let me out of here!
Let me out! Gotcha!
Time to snap your spear in half!
Damn it.
All right, at least I'm
finally free of those cords.
Now I've got to send Chariot under the
bed and get myself the hell out of here.
Great.
Now what's he doing?
Hey, Polnareff, how would you like it
if I took a bite out of your balls?
I can't believe that a doll could
be such an obscene little jerk.
I'm done!
Whoa there!
I'm gonna run off to a
place you can't see now!
You numbskull!
Give the floor you're
stuck to a good feel!
Go ahead, moron!
What? This is...
The carpet's soaked with
beer, juice, and alcohol!
You have a well-stocked
bar that I put to good use!
If I had piss in me, I would have
soaked you in it to make it even wetter!
Oh, look, a hairdryer.
And it's lit up like a fireworks
show at a summer festival.
There's so many uses for it.
Which one do you think I'm
going to pick, Polnareff?
Now you can style that
ridiculous hair of yours.
Die.
Time to put an end to this curse.
Meet your maker, Polnareff.
Hm, you're not the only one who can break
stuff, you satanic little pincushiet!
What?
How did you know precisely
where I was on top of the bed?
I trapped you underneath it!
Simple, I broke all the mirrors, so
I could see you hanging over the bed?
clear as day from down here.
Sucks to be you!
At last we meet.
Whoa there!
Now then, I have a question.
I seek a man with two right hands.
He has something to answer for.
Save me some trouble and tell
me what his stand is. You idiot!
No assassin worth a damn would
ever reveal his stand's identity.
It only happens in the face of
certain death for him or his opponent!
You guys are so stupid, always showing
off your stands everywhere you go!
It's your own fault that we know all your
weaknesses if it weren't for that mirror.
I would have killed you You're
just a moron who got lucky.
All right, then come at me!
What's the matter didn't
you say you were going
to bite off my balls
or something tough guy?
Go ahead and try it
I dare you you vulgar little shit.
I am gonna
Everything except your balls
You are home!
Excuse me, sir.
It seems you've been in the
bathroom for quite some time.
Are you feeling all right?
Polnareff, you're finally here. Yeah.
You're not terribly punctual
and you look like hell.
Okay, let's get right to it.
Let's figure out what our strategy
will be of soul-sacrifice attacks.
Polnareff, pay attention.
You're...
joking, right?
Answer me, punk!
Why was there a dead
boy's body in your room?
And what about the dead body
that was in the bathroom?
The two are connected, aren't they?
Answer me now!
I have the right to
remain silent, officer.
Huh?
You finally showed up!
I've been waiting a while!
I had the Speedwagon
Foundation strike a deal.
Polnareff should be released soon
enough, without too much hassle.
But that was cutting
it close, even for us.
To think that the enemy's
pursuit would come so early on...
Don't forget that Dio's body used
to belong to Jonathan Joestar.
While they're united, he'll
know everything Jotaro and I do.
That's why his minions'
attacks are relentless.
But we can use that against him and
read his thoughts just as he reads ours.
Hmm.
Shall I go buy a camera?
That won't be necessary.
I can use my powers even
without a camera. What?
Michael is still not here.
Where the hell is he?
This week's number three jumps
up five points from last week.
In trading, the price
of gold today wrote...
You look delicious!
Oh, no!
Very strange.
The channels are changing as if
the TV has a mind of its own.
It's searching for words from among the
channels and connecting
them into a sentence.
Creating a message for
the ear not the eye.
There I think the first part is there.
Is wait what was that?
What the hell did it just say?
I could be wrong but I think it said that
there is a traitor who
is walking among us.
Servant!
Kakyoin? What? It can't be!
That's impossible.
Kakyoin is Dio's servant?
This is...
Joestar, you bastard.
You're watching me.
Well, watch this!
Dio!
He found us! Look out!
But that can't be true, can it?
You know as well as I do.
Hermit Purple says Kakyoin is a traitor,
a servant to Dio who will at
some point betray all of us.
It can't be!
There must be a reason.
I won't believe Kakyoin is a traitor.
There has to be an explanation.
We'll have to be even more alert.
If he is still connected with Dio,
he could exterminate any one
of us while we're sleeping.
He'd be just like Dio's
very own Trojan horse.
So then, where is Kakyoin?
He's with Jotaro.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick!
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got their money on
a bed Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling tacks with a hookah. I say!
Walk
like
an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays,
spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves you drop your
drink then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of folks
they like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings they're
walking like an egyptian!
All the kids in the marketplace say? Walk
like
an Egyptian.
Thank you.